guitarzero2hero.com 2019-06-18

# Privacy Policy - GuitarZero2Hero

**Please read the following statements carefully, as they address the rules of engagement between us.**

Your privacy is critically important to us. We want to assure you we respect your data protection rights in compliance with the latest EU General Data Protection Regulation ([GDPR](https://www.eugdpr.org/)) requirements as of 25th May 2018.

This Website is owned and operated by GuitarZero2Hero. The following terms and conditions govern your use of this site and all other GuitarZero2Hero and products.

For the purpose of this agreement and for ease of use, any reference to “the Company” shall be a reference to GuitarZero2Hero and any reference to “the Website” shall be a reference to any and all websites owned by the Company, their respective products, and their employees and agents.

The Websites include, but are not limited to: guitarzero2hero.com.

By accessing this Website and any of the Company’s properties, you are acknowledging and accepting the conditions of this Privacy Policy for all of the Company’s properties.

These terms of use are subject to change at any time at the discretion of the Company without notice. Your use of any of the Company’s Websites after any changes are implemented constitutes your acceptance of the changes. As a result, we encourage you to consult the terms and conditions herein frequently.

We have a few fundamental principles:

  * We do not actively collect sensitive information about you, including information about your health, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, sexual orientation or criminal history. We will take steps to appropriately protect any sensitive information we do receive.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation and delivery of our services to you.
  * We store personal information only for as long as we have a reason to keep it.
  * In our email communications we give you the option to unsubscribe from email communications with us at any time from the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails.

 **TYPE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Like most website operators, we collect (via its Websites) non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.

Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our Websites.

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We do not use such information to identify our visitors, and do not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personally-identifying information, as described above.

Certain visitors to our Websites choose to interact with us in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information like email address, name and surname (to name some). The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction.

We collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with us. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our Websites.**

 **PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our Websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our Websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information, only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of the Company, third parties or the public at large.

 **HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

If you are a registered user of any of our Websites and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new lesson updates, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with products that may be of interest to you.

We are committed to delivering only information and educational material we deem will be relevant and of benefit to you. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum.

We take all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

 **AGGREGATED STATISTICS**

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our websites. We may display this information publicly but will not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described above.

 **COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

Cookies are small text files of information stored by your internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use cookies to collect browsing data, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information and to collect general usage and volume statistical information. Our cookies do not collect personal, confidential information and are not spyware.

You may set your internet web browser to refuse cookies or to remove cookies from your hard drive.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Company uses cookies to help the Company identify and track visitors, their usage of The Company’s Websites, and their Websites access preferences. The Company’s visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Company’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of the Company’s Websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **ADS**

If any ads appear on any of our Websites, they may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **YOUR CONSENT**

By using any of the Company’s Websites you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **CHOICE/OPT-OUT**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails at any time, by following the unsubscribe instructions included in any of our emails, by updating your communications preferences via our email service provider, or you can contact us via our [Support page](https://guitarzero2hero.com/contact).

 **TESTIMONIALS**

If you provide us with a testimonial, you give us your consent for the use of your name and the Service to be displayed on any of our Websites, or in our other marketing materials, together with the content of the testimonial that you provide.

 **COMMENTS**

Comments and other content submitted to our sites are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

 **TERMINATION**

We may cancel or terminate your right to use some or any of our sites or any part of those sites at any time without notice, and at our discretion. In the event of cancellation or termination, you are no longer authorized to access the part or parts of the sites affected by such cancellation or termination. The restrictions imposed on you with respect to material downloaded from any of our sites, and the disclaimers and limitations of liabilities set forth in these Terms of Service, shall survive.

 **CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

The Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 12. We will not knowingly collect personal information from them. If we discover that a child has provided us with personal information, we will use reasonable efforts to delete this information.

If you have reason to believe we may have accidentally received personal information from a child under the age of 12, please immediately submit details through our Support page.

 **ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

You have the right under the Data Protection Act to access the information which we hold about you. If you wish to exercise this right, please send your request to us via our [Support page](https://guitarzero2hero.com/contact). 

**ABOUT THE PRIVACY POLICY**

If you do not understand any of the contents in this Privacy Policy, or if you have any questions or comments, we invite you to contact us via our [Support page](https://guitarzero2hero.com/contact).

 _This Privacy Policy was last updated May 2018._
